prettydesigns.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Pretty Designs

[Home](http://www.prettydesigns.com/) » Privacy Policy

Prettydesigns.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. Please take a moment to read our policy explaining our use of the personal information that you provide and the choices you can make about the collection and use of your information by Prettydesigns.com.

 **Providing personal information**

At Prettydesigns.com, we provide many interactive features which allow you to vote in polls, provide commentary on our features, participate in online forums, and subscribe to our magazine online. While you may use many of the features of the website without providing any personal information, we may at times ask that you provide us with certain information so that we may perform the service you request.

This information may include, but is not limited to, your name, e-mail or home address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, birth date, gender, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

We will never collect personal information from you without your knowledge or consent, and you may always choose not to provide the information we request. Please note, however, that if you do not provide us with this information, you may be unable to access some of the features of the website.

 **How we use personal information**

From time to time, we may use the personal information you provide us to send you information regarding Prettydesigns.com features and subscriptions. We may use the information to contact you about your account or to notify you in the event that you win one of our contests or sweepstakes. We may also offer you other products, programs, or services that we believe may be of interest to you. You will always have the choice to opt out of receiving these offers, updates, and information. If you provide us with credit card information in order to make a purchase from our website, we will share that information with the credit card company in order to complete your purchase. We may disclose personal information at the request of a law enforcement agency or when compelled by a court order or subpoena to do so.

If you submit written content, for example, a comment on a posting or a letter to the editor, to Prettydesigns.com, we may publish information about you that you provide, such as your name, screen name, and hometown along with your content.

 **Non-personally identifiable information**

We may collect non-personally identifiable information, for example, the type of operating system you use to access our website, the domain name of your internet service provider, and the type of browser you are using. We use this information to improve many of the features of Prettydesigns.com; we may also use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage and to provide data to our advertisers.

 **Minors**

Prettydesigns.com is not intended for children. If you are below the age of 13, we ask that you not submit any personal information to this website. In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), we will not accept any registrations or any other personal information from those under the age of 13. More information on COPPA is available here.

 **Cookies**

We use cookies, as well as other tracking programs, for various features on Prettydesigns.com. A “Cookie” is a small data file that is able to store certain information when you visit a website. We may use cookies to perform such services as saving your password in password-protected areas and remembering your video plug-in preferences so that you do not have to reset them each time you visit our site. We may also use cookies to track how often visitors are visiting Prettydesigns.com, which pages are visited most often, and user preferences. Cookies will not allow us access to personal information which you have not already provided to us. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so by turning them off in your web browser. While many parts of Prettydesigns.com will still be accessible to you if you choose to disable cookies, you may be unable to use certain features of the website.

 **Security information**

We take the protection of your personal information seriously. Our databases are stored in a secure location and your information is guarded by firewalls and other technology. Although we take appropriate precautions to ensure the security of your information, we cannot assure you that the personal information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.

 **Changes to the policy**

From time to time, we may make changes to the guidelines and content of our policy. These changes will always be posted at this location on our website. In order to keep yourself fully informed of our privacy policy information, we encourage you to periodically review this policy.

 **Third party advertising and websites**

We use a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit Prettydesigns.com. This company may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to our website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by this company, please click here.

Prettydesigns.com may contain links to other websites. The privacy policies of these websites may be different than those listed here, and we do not have any control over, and are not responsible for, the information or use of this information that these websites collect. Please read the privacy notices of any third party websites for their policies.

The owner of this website, prettydesigns.com, is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking prettydesigns.com to Amazon properties including, but not limited to, amazon.com, endless.com, myhabit.com, smallparts.com, or amazonwireless.com.

From time to time, Prettydesigns.com may offer promotions, contests, or sweepstakes that are sponsored or co-sponsored by other companies. These companies may have access to the personal information you provide in order to participate in these promotions, sweepstakes, or contests. We do not have any control over, and are not responsible for, our sponsors’ or co-sponsors’ use of this information.

 **Sale or Bankruptcy Information**

In the event of a bankruptcy, sale, merger, public offering, or other change in control of Prettydesigns.com, your information may be shared with the person or business that assumes ownership or control of this website.
